>> Brian Holt: 因此，让我们一起使用上下文，因此 Context.js 在此处。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So let's go down to use
Context, so Context.js right here.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，注意我有第一级，第二级，第三级，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now, notice I have first
level, second level, third level,
第四层我有詹姆斯 - 詹姆森的长子
fourth level, and
then I have James Jameson the firstborn.
我想我喝了几杯威士忌
I think I was a couple of whiskeys deep,
so
那是我最能创造的
that's the most creativity I could muster.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，上下文正在解决此问题。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
context is solving this problem.
如果你需要了解更多的背景
Which, if you need to
know more about context,
我恳求您让 Intro to React， cuz 关于 context的对话。
I implore you to take the Intro to React,
cuz that talks about context.
但是要告诉你，它解决了
But just to tell you, it solves the
problem of having to do prop drilling of
将父代传递给子代，父级与子代，以及覆盖 Redux 的内容
passing parent to child, parent to child,
as well as covering things that Redux
通常包括应用程序级别状态。
would normally cover,
which is like application-level state.
所以我要用一个假的物体来创造一个情境。
So here I'm creating
a context with a fake object.
这只是让人们知道物体的形状。
This is just letting people
know the shape of the object.
这是一个更新的功能。
And this is an updater function.
或者这在技术上被称为身份功能
Or this would be called
an identity function technically,
但并不是它真的需要这么做
but not that it really needs to be that.
但只要说这就是钩子的形状
But suffice to say this
is the shape of a hook.
好吗 ?
Okay?
这里才是最重要的五级，对吧 ?
Here is actually where this matters,
here on levelFive, right?
我创造这个的地方就在下面
Where I create this, well,
that's down here at the bottom, so
让我们从这一级开始
let's actually start all the way
down here at the level one.
或者是 ContextComponent 。
Or ContextComponent, rather.
我在创造一个用国家的钩子，对吧 ?
So here,
I'm creating a useState hook, right?
詹姆斯 - 詹姆森一号和他的邮箱地址
With the name James Jameson 1 and
his email address.
但我可以把这个完全改变给鲍勃之类的对吧
But I could totally change this to Bob or
something like that, right?
会在这里发生变化的通知。
Notice that would change down here.
但我在顶级组件中创造了这个
But I'm creating this in
the top-level component.
我把这个供应商放在上面
I'm putting this provider above it.
然后我就会下降到第二级
And then I'm rendering down to level two.
3 级， 4 级，然后 5 级。
Level three, level four,
and then level five here.
在这里我正在阅读这方面的内容。
Here I'm reading through the context.
请注意，我没有通过这些不同级别的组件。
Notice I didn't pass it through all these
various different levels of components.
但我正在用 useContext 从这里读出来，好吗 ?
But I'm reading out of the context
here using useContext, all right?
然后我就会得到用户并在这里设置用户。
So then I get user and set user down here.
如果我点击增量就会增加
And here if I click increment,
it's incrementing this
尽管钩子的生命都在这里
despite the fact that the hook
lives all the way up here.
因此 useContext 允许您以这种方式读取和写入上下文。
So useContext allows you to read and
write to context in this fashion.
>> Brian Holt: 有关 useContext的任何问题 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Any
questions about useContext?
再一次，在  中有一个完整的章节。
Again, there’s a whole section on
it in the Complete Intro to React.
所以如果你的背景让你困惑的话，我恳请你看看
So if context itself is confusing to you,
I’d implore you to take a look at that